(Howard:)It's smashed beyond repair.
What are you gonna do with it?
(Raj:)What else?
Sell it on eBay as slightly used.
(Leonard:)It was Penny's boyfriend's.
They broke up.
(Howard:)Apparently, he posted intimate details
of their physical relationship on his blog...
(Howard:)...which I cannot find anywhere.
You know what? I'm gonna go back
and try talking to her again.
(Howard:)Good idea.
Sit with her, hold her, comfort her.
(Howard:)And if the moment feels right,
see if you can cop a feel.
(Leonard:)I'm not going to do that, Howard.
(Sheldon:)I'm not aware of any social convention
that requires you to intervene at all.
What about damsel in distress?
Twelfth-century code of chivalry?
Not exactly current.
(Sheldon:)You'd also have to be knighted
for that to apply.
(Leonard:)I don't care.
She's upset, I'm going over there.
(Howard:)Remember to sit on your hands a bit
so they're warm.
(Leonard:)I'm her friend. I'm not going
to take advantage of her vulnerability.
So you're saying, if in the depths of despair
she throws herself at you...